careerperfect.com 2002-10-11

# CareerPerfect® Privacy Policy

|   
---  
| Expert advice  
| Find your dream career  
| My Personal Profile™  
| Ensure the right job fit  
| Expert advice  
| Résumé writing services  
| Sample résumés & letters  
| e-Résumé tutorial  
| Expert advice  
| InterviewSmart™ – Online   
| Advice & strategy  
| Distribute your résumé  
| Job databases  
| Post your résumé  
| Contacts for executives  
| Salary surveys  
| Relocation tools  
| Checklist  
| Featured topics  
| Career development  
| Virtual outplacement  
| [Network with others  
or ask a question](http://forum.careerperfect.com/WebX?@0.k6vIlaAn^0@)  
| Safe & secure  
| Our privacy policy  
| Join Partners & Affiliates  
| Contact us  
| Advertising  
| Search  
| Help  
| Downloads  
| Site Index  
| Home  
| Links  
| Report a broken link  
| About CareerPerfect®  
  |   
| 

####    
Privacy Policy

**CareerPerfect.com's Privacy Commitment - Overview**  
CareerPerfect.com is committed to protecting the privacy of our users. We want to provide a safe, secure user experience. We will use our best efforts to ensure that the information you submit to us remains private, and is used only for the purposes as set forth herein. 

**The Following Reflects Our Commitment To You**  
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the CareerPerfect.com and Monster.CareerPerfect.com websites. 

**Information About All CareerPerfect.com Visitors**  
In general, we gather information about all of our users collectively, such as what areas users visit most frequently and what services users access the most. We only use such data anonymously and in the aggregate. This information helps us determine what is most beneficial for our users, and how we can continually create a better overall experience for you. We may share this information with our partners, but only in the aggregate, so that they too may understand how CareerPerfect.com visitors use our site, so they may create a better overall experience for you, as well. 

**Information About You Specifically**  
In some instances, when you sign up to use a service, enter into a contest, or purchase a product or service, for example, we may need more specific information about you, such as name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, credit card number, type of computer, etc. If you give us permission, we may use that information to make you aware of additional products and services that may be of interest to you or to contact you regarding site changes. 

CareerPerfect.com also provides you with the opportunity to opt-out of these types of communications. If you choose to receive these types of communications at the time of registration or ordering, but later decide you no longer want to receive them, simply send an e-mail to [admin@CareerPerfect.com](mailto:admin@CareerPerfect.com) and type "remove" in the subject line.

During your visit to CareerPerfect.com, we may also ask you for other information, such as information on your interests, your likes and dislikes regarding the site, the types of jobs you are interested in, etc., in an effort to deliver to you the best possible site experience. 

**General Information Disclosure**  
Except as described in this privacy policy, we do not disclose information about your individual visits to CareerPerfect.com, or personal information that you provide, such as your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, credit card number, personal references, etc., to any outside parties, except when we believe it is required by law or to protect CareerPerfect.com, our users or others. But, we may record and share aggregated information with our partners. Also, if you input your information on a co-branded order or registration page, such as that of a CareerPerfect.com and partner company-sponsored product, service, or contest, then your information becomes the property of both CareerPerfect.com and the partner co-sponsoring the product, service or contest. In that instance, the use of your personal information by our partner company will be subject to the privacy policy of that company and CareerPerfect.com is not responsible for their use of your personal information. 

We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples may include hosting our web servers, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. These other companies will have access to your personal information as necessary to perform their functions, but they may not share that information with any third party. 

**Resumes**  
Your resume and all the information submitted for preparation of your resume is considered strictly private, and unless we believe we are required by law to do so, CareerPerfect.com will not disclose that information to anyone without your authorization, provided in accordance with your opt-out/opt-in elections at registration or upon ordering with us, or thereafter, consistent with your changes to such elections at any time. 

**Assessments  
**When you purchase a career planning software program and take the included assessments, all of your assessment results are strictly private, CareerPerfect.com will not disclose that information to anyone without your authorization. CareerPerfect will only provide to its career assessment publishing partners the information needed to score and provide you with your assessment results. CareerPerfect will never disclose your assessment results to any third party, unless we believe we are required by law to do so.

**Online Order Security** When you place an order online, your personal details and credit card information are scrambled using industry-standard SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) encryption technology before being sent over the Internet. Although we cannot guarantee encryption or the privacy of your personal details and credit card information, SSL makes it very difficult for your information to be stolen or intercepted while being transferred. Our Credit Card transactions are maintained by a company called Authorize.net. All information sent to Authorize.net is encrypted, which will protect it against disclosure to third parties. When we receive your order, it is kept encrypted until they're ready to process it. For further information about Authorize.net's privacy and security practices, please [click here](http://www.authorize.net/). 

**Cookies** To enhance your experience at CareerPerfect.com, we use a feature on your Internet browser called a "cookie". Cookies are small files that your Web browser places on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies for remembering user names and passwords and preferences, ensuring purchases are completed successfully, taking online assessments to enable you to access your results, tracking click streams, and for load balancing,. Because of our use of cookies, we can deliver faster service, consistent, updated results, and a more personalized site experience. You have the option of setting your browser to reject cookies. However, doing this will hinder performance and negatively impact your experience on some parts of our site. 

**Feedback** CareerPerfect.com has an area on the site where you can submit feedback. Any feedback that is submitted through this area becomes the property of CareerPerfect.com. We may use this feedback, such as success stories, for marketing purposes, or to contact you for further feedback on the site. 

**Children** We do not specifically collect information about children. We believe that children should get their parents' consent before giving out personal information. If you are concerned about your child's use of CareerPerfect.com, we encourage you to use Web filtering technology to supervise your child's access to the site. We also encourage you to participate in your child's experience with CareerPerfect.com. With a little guidance, the site can prove very useful inproviding them with excellent career guidance information. 

**Privacy Commitment Changes** If we decide to change our privacy commitment for CareerPerfect.com, we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose it to anyone. If, at any time, you have questions or concerns about CareerPerfect.com's privacy commitment, please feel free to email us at [admin@CareerPerfect.com](mailto:admin@CareerPerfect.com) or call 1-800-573-3344 and speak to one of our representatives. 

Thank you for using CareerPerfect.com. We'll keep working hard to earn your loyalty.

|   | Visit ****Safe and Secure to learn how ordering with CareerPerfect.com is fast, easy, and safe!  
---|---  
  
* * *

[Copyright © 1996 - 2001](http://ww1.careerperfect.com/CareerPerfect/UserLic.htm) Career Services Group, Inc. All rights reserved.  
[Terms of use](http://ww1.careerperfect.com/CareerPerfect/UserLic.htm).

|   

Bookmark this page!  
(Press Ctrl-D)
